<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on harry morley</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on harry morley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>goldcomparts.show</title>
      <link>/posts/goldcomparts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/goldcomparts/</guid>
      <description>This is the website I made for my final degree show, &amp;ldquo;So, How is That Working For You?&amp;rdquo; (5-8 Sept 2019). Map implemented by Julia Makivic.
Built using Hugo, the static site generator, HTML/CSS3 and JavaScript (no libraries). Makes use of a monospace font and the &amp;ldquo;ch&amp;rdquo; unit in CSS to perfectly align the ASCII art design to the grid.
Visit goldcomparts.show
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cellular Orchestra</title>
      <link>/posts/cellular-orchestra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cellular-orchestra/</guid>
      <description>Cellular Orchestra</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>t-SNE Sampler (machine learning project)</title>
      <link>/posts/tsne-sampler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tsne-sampler/</guid>
      <description>I completed this project as part of Rebecca Fiebrink&amp;rsquo;s Data and Machine Learning module at Goldsmiths. It uses the t-SNE algorithm to reduce the number of dimensions of audio analysis data, so that sounds are arranged in 2D space according to their likeness to one another. I used around 600 sounds, consisting of royalty free samples and my own field recordings.
For example, all the kick drums are together, all of the wooden percussion sounds are near eachother, and the hi-hat sounds are grouped - and suitably far away from the kick samples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>openCV Mini Projects</title>
      <link>/posts/cv-mini-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cv-mini-projects/</guid>
      <description>Collection of small computer vision sketches.
 Projects Webcam Harp  openFrameworks/C++ with ofxCv and ofxMaxim libraries.
 Face-controlled generative visuals  2D graphics controlled by Kyle Mcdonald&amp;rsquo;s FaceOSC face tracker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A/V Mini Projects</title>
      <link>/posts/av-mini-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/av-mini-projects/</guid>
      <description>Collection of mini projects completed over the year as part of my MA in Computational Arts at Goldsmiths. Image processing algorithms coded from scratch using openFrameworks/C++, audio projects use openFrameworks/C++ with the ofxMaxim library.
 Projects Image manipulator Skews and ripples an image, in this case Monet&amp;rsquo;s Waterlilies.
 Interactive AV sketch  Graphics based on FAL&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Motion Catalog&amp;rdquo;, ported to openFrameworks/C++ by myself, with sonified using the ofxMaxim library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topographic Drummer</title>
      <link>/posts/topographic-drummer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/topographic-drummer/</guid>
      <description>This project is an exploration into using 2D data from different shapes to sequence and synthesize percussion sounds. It is a performable program designed for improvisation and on-the-fly beat creation, particularly with a minimal and microsound aesthetic. The user can put shapes on a canvas, modify parameters, send the shapes off in random directions and toggle a glitchy delay effect.
Each drum uses simple subtractive synthesis methods from the Maximilian library, consisting of a sine/saw/triangle wave, state variable filter and envelope for shaping percussive sounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invisible Clouds (projection mapping project)</title>
      <link>/posts/invisible-clouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/invisible-clouds/</guid>
      <description>My projection mapping project for Workshops in Creative Coding. Coded in openFrameworks/C++ using the ofxPiMapper addon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside Voice - Joey Dosik (Studio Cover)</title>
      <link>/posts/inside-voice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/inside-voice/</guid>
      <description>Went to Air Studios, London and had the pleasure of playing a very old Hammond B3 and Minimoog, on a cover of Joey Dosik&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Inside Voice&amp;rdquo;, alongside some talented friends. Psychedelic phone video edited by myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polar Twin - PT03</title>
      <link>/posts/pt03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pt03/</guid>
      <description>PT03 is a short split single.   soup : cool water by POLAR TWIN</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Live</title>
      <link>/posts/game-of-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/game-of-live/</guid>
      <description>A sonification of John Conway’s Game of Life, the famous cellular automaton. Built in Ableton’s Max for Live, the system treats an iterating 2D grid as a generative arpeggiator, which outputs MIDI to a synth. Each cell of the grid can be alive or dead, the state of which is determined by a simple set of rules based on the number of neighbours it has.
Visuals coded in Processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set of Three</title>
      <link>/posts/set-of-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/set-of-three/</guid>
      <description>This piece was a study in sample manipulation using Max/MSP and a custom multitouch interface for iPad (using Mira). The patch I built manipulated intimate piano samples, using granular synthesis and time stretching to create a glitchy, delicate atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polar Twin - PT02</title>
      <link>/posts/pt02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pt02/</guid>
      <description> &amp;lsquo;in hush tone&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;more ambient drones n tones to chill ur bones&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;best heard at low volumes late at night&amp;rsquo;
in hush tone by porcelain chambers </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>_butterflies (Lorenz Attractor sonification)</title>
      <link>/posts/butterflies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/butterflies/</guid>
      <description>A sonification of the Lorenz Attractor, a chaotic system made up of 3 differential equations. Programmed in Max/MSP + Jitter, the system derives melodic content from the x, y and z values of 2 simultaneously running Lorenz systems, as well as the distance between them, illustrating the butterfly effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take My Hand - Matt Berry (Studio Cover)</title>
      <link>/posts/take-my-hand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/take-my-hand/</guid>
      <description>Played keys on this cover of the Toast of London theme tune with some wonderful people! Recorded and produced by Ashley Andrew-Jones and Paul Anders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polar Twin - PT01</title>
      <link>/posts/pt01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pt01/</guid>
      <description> First release (split LP) on Polar Twin Records, a new experimental project with Luke Phillips. Visuals put together by myself using free software, some running water and a bin bag.
PT01 by POLAR TWIN </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Sonifications</title>
      <link>/posts/image-sonifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/image-sonifications/</guid>
      <description>Below are a set of sonifications I made of 3 famous works of art. I built a simple sonification system in Processing that simplifies an image of the artwork into an array of large circular pixels. The program then ‘plays’ the pixels as notes by selecting them at random, which triggers notes using HSB (hue, saturation, brightness) data to derive pitches and rhythms.
When a pixel is triggered, 2 notes are played simultaneously.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>